<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deployo Blog on Deployo</title>
    <link>https://deployo.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deployo Blog on Deployo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://deployo.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Force HTTPS on Heroku</title>
      <link>https://deployo.me/blog/https-heroku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deployo.me/blog/https-heroku/</guid>
      <description>Recently I deployed and app to Heroku and I wanted to force my users to only access it over HTTPS. I tried finding a configuration option in the Heroku dashboard but found nothing, then I stumbeled upon this help page and the following sentence: &amp;ldquo;Redirects need to be performed at the application level as the Heroku router does not provide this functionality. You should code the redirect logic into your application&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interservice communication with Docker and Dokku</title>
      <link>https://deployo.me/blog/interservice-communication-docker-dokku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deployo.me/blog/interservice-communication-docker-dokku/</guid>
      <description>Dokku is a wonderfull tool if you want to run you own Heroku-like platform where you can host a number of your applications. It helps you set up your deployment, database connection, nginx configuration and even SSL with Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt.
Dokku makes runing your application and connecting it to a database very easy, but what if you have multiple applications that need to talk to each other?
Let&amp;rsquo;s say that you have an application and a database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install and manage Dokku on Linode</title>
      <link>https://deployo.me/blog/install-and-manage-dokku-on-linode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://deployo.me/blog/install-and-manage-dokku-on-linode/</guid>
      <description>Dokku is a Heroku-like &amp;ldquo;docker-powered PaaS that helps you build and manage the lifecycle of applications&amp;rdquo;, as it says on its GitHub page. It has a similar git-centric interface for running and managing your applications.
I will show you how to install and use Dokku on a Linode instance. I will be using Deployo to manage the server but you can also just SSH into the server and execute the same commands.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>